People who systematically underestimate themselves and their own performance suffer from the so-called Impostor Phenomenon.
那些一贯低估自己、低估自身表现的人，受所谓“冒名顶替现象”的困扰。
They think that any success is due to external circumstances or just luck and chance.
他们认为，任何成功都是外部环境使然，或者仅仅是运气和偶然。
Those people live in constant fear that their “deception” will be exposed.
这些人时刻生活在恐惧中，担心自己的“骗局”会被揭穿。
It is common for people to question their abilities now and again.
人们时不时怀疑自己的能力，这很常见。
A healthy amount of reflection and self-doubt can protect a person from acting impulsively.
适度的反思和自我怀疑能够防止人冲动行事。
However, there are people who are permanently plagued by a massive amount of self-doubt despite delivering a good performance.
然而，有些人尽管表现良好，却一直饱受强烈的自我怀疑困扰。
They think that none of their successes are a product of their skill or hard work; instead, they attribute their own successes to external circumstances, for example, to luck and chance, or believe that their performance is massively overestimated by others.
他们认为，自己的成功没有一次是自身技能或努力的结果；相反，他们把自己的成功归因于外部环境，比如运气和偶然，或者认为别人大大高估了自己的表现。
Failures, on the other hand, are always internalised as the result of their own shortcomings.
另一方面，他们总是把失败归咎于自身的缺点。
Psychologists from Martin Luther University Halle-Wittenberg examined the topic for the first time under real-life conditions.
哈勒-维滕贝格马丁·路德大学的心理学家首次在真实生活条件下研究了这一课题。
Seventy-six participants completed a range of intelligence tests and received positive feedback on them, regardless of their actual performance.
76名参与者完成了一系列智力测试，而且无论实际表现如何，都得到了正面的测试反馈。
They were then asked why they thought they did so well.
随后，他们被问及为什么认为自己表现得这么好。
The study showed two things: First, the self-reported degree of Impostor Phenomenon is not related to actual measured intelligence or performance.
研究表明了两点：第一，自我报告的冒名顶替现象程度与实际测得的智力或表现无关。
Secondly, the test supported the assumption that people with a tendency to exhibit the Impostor Phenomenon devalue their objectively measured performance and attribute positive results to external causes such as luck and chance, but not to their own abilities.
第二，该测试支持了这样一个假设：倾向于表现出冒名顶替现象的人会贬低自己客观测得的表现，并把正面结果归因于运气和偶然等外部原因，而不是归因于自己的能力。
These results are also completely unrelated to age and gender.
这些结果也与年龄和性别完全无关。
A permanent underestimation of one’s own abilities is often accompanied by the fear that this supposed intellectual deception will be exposed sooner or later and that they will pay the price for this.
长期低估自身能力，往往伴随着这样的恐惧：担心这种想象中的智力骗局迟早会被揭穿，自己也会为此付出代价。
The Impostor Phenomenon was first described in 1978 by U.S. psychologists Pauline Clance and Suzanne Imes.
1978年，美国心理学家葆琳·克兰斯和苏珊娜·艾姆斯首次描述了冒名顶替现象。
They observed that there is a particularly high number of successful women who do not think they are very intelligent.
她们观察到，不认为自己很聪明的成功女性特别多。
The Impostor Phenomenon is not defined as a mental illness.
冒名顶替现象并未被界定为一种精神疾病。
However, people who suffer from it show a higher vulnerability to depression.
然而，受其困扰的人更容易患抑郁症。